{
    "id": "76b38d0732cc4e0e95e6d4313e2f6f7b",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. tact would have saved the situation.",
            "description": "Little means hardly any a little means some, but not much.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the three, opera, movies and music, the ………………………. is his favorite.",
            "description": "Use latter when there are only two things.",
            "answers": [
                "later",
                "latter",
                "last"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… book you mention is out of print.",
            "description": "We use ‘the’ to speak of a particular person or thing.",
            "answers": [
                "The",
                "A"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I dislike ………………………. fellow.",
            "description": "We use ‘the’ to speak of a particular person or thing.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. darkest cloud has a silver lining.",
            "description": "We use the with superlatives.",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Banaras is …………………… holy city.",
            "description": "We use ‘a’ in the numerical sense of one.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Alladin had ……………………. magic lamp.",
            "description": "We use ‘a’ in the numerical sense of one.",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. scheme failed for want of support.",
            "description": "We use ‘the’ to speak of a particular person or thing.",
            "answers": [
                "A",
                "The"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. people want a new system.",
            "description": "We use most before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "The most",
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. these doors leads to the hall.",
            "description": "We use neither of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Neither of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… the green apples were given to Sarah.",
            "description": "We use six of before a noun with an article, possessive or demonstrative.",
            "answers": [
                "Six",
                "Six of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. of my friends smoke.",
            "description": "No is not used before of. Instead we use none.",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "None",
                "Not any"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}